You, familiar spirit!
(Out!)
I say, you familiar spirit!
I say, these familiar spirits cause sickness and disease!
Whatever these familiar spirits might have caused you, its name is demon!
Its name is satan, destruction, killer!
You familiar spirits, we say to you, whatever you caused them – go out!
Go out!
Go out with your sickness, disease, failure, setback, nightmare, limitation! Out!
Out!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Don't come near me!
Please!
I am the queen of the river!
People of God: Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
My name is Ngozi Christiana Njoku
The girl standing beside me is my daughter, and next to her is my lovely mother.
It started when I was young.
In the village, a girl asked me to go to the stream with her.
I said, "OK, let's go to the stream" and I went with her.
When we got to the stream, she was teaching me how to swim.
Later on, I realised I was far out in a river and I felt something pulling my leg strongly -
it was trying to pull me under the water.
So, I started screaming and a lady came and pulled me out of the river.
I thought everything was over, I went to my house and I didn't tell my mother or father.
In time, I started having strange dreams and strange things would happen to me.
I would see snakes and a woman coming to crown me in my dreams.
She was a very beautiful woman wearing a gown and a crown on her head.
She would always come in my dreams to put a crown on my head.
As time went on, I thought everything was over; I didn't explain my experience to anybody.
I was in primary school then, after primary school, I went to secondary school.
When I got into the secondary school, a lady came to me and said that she was my 'school mother'.
I became bi-sexual and I became pregnant but the boy said he was not the father
and he didn't know anything about it.
I told him there was no problem then, I called my parents in Cameroon
and told my mother all that had happened to me.
She said, "My daughter, don't worry, everything will be over.
After delivery, carry the child and come over to us here in Cameroon."
After I delivered my daughter, I took her to Cameroon; she was two months old.
She started growing up with my parents but along the line, I saw that she was living the same life I was living.
I said, "God, what is happening to us?"
What happened to me was that I would see women like men, I didn't value men.
That was what happened to me after the woman crowned me in the dream.
OK. You said that later on you got involved in a relationship with a man and gave birth to your daughter,
who stands beside you.
Can you tell us at what age you gave birth to your daughter?
At the age of 14, I gave birth to my daughter.
I saw she was living the same life I was living and she also got pregnant at the age of 14.
I made her abort two pregnancies.
She was disturbing everyone in the house, she would not sleep in the house, she would go out and smoke.
I was worried, so I went to all the herbalists in Cameroon.
They finished all my money; I am a hairdresser by profession.
The last herbalist told me to give him money so he would buy a live snake and bury the snake in a coffin.
I gave him money and bought the coffin; he buried them but everything became worse.
I didn’t know what was happening.
What was the purpose of your going to this native doctor, who requested a live snake to bury it?
What was the purpose of going to all these native doctors?
I went to the native doctor because of my daughter, not even for my own case.
But after performing all these sacrifices nothing happened?
Nothing happened, except that case got worse and worse.
Can you now tell us more about the lifestyle you lived, as a result of your encounter with the queen of the cost?
Tell us more about the lifestyle and your experiences in life.
The experience I had was that man would come and propose to me with engagement rings
but later, they would go and not come back.
I began to wonder what was happening to me, at my age I was not married;
I didn’t know it was the spirit woman that was disturbing me.
I was watching Emmanuel TV and said to myself,
‘If this beautiful lady could stand and testify to the world what the Lord has done then, who am I?
I know I am proud of myself but I will put my pride and beauty aside.
I know that one day, God will see me through and I will testify of what He has done for me’.
That was how I decided to travel back home to Nigeria.
That was last Friday but my daughter knew I had planned to come to The SCOAN.
She left the house on Friday and didn’t come home.
I was crying to God as I didn’t understand what was happening;
when I called her phone, she was not answering my call.
I prayed and said, “God of T.B. Joshua, wherever this girl is, please bring her home”.
It was already late in the afternoon.
I was sleeping and my phone rang, it was my daughter saying,
"Mummy, I'm coming back; don’t be angry, I don’t want you to beat me."
I told her that I would not beat her and that she would come,
so we could go where we had planned to go – we would get the night bus.
That was how we left our place and came here.
So, that Sunday, you were at The SCOAN.
Can you tell us what actually happened on that day?
I had stopped going to church; I hadn't gone to church for four to five years.
So, when I entered the gates I made a vow to God that I would continue going to church.
When it was time for Mass Prayer, a spirit asked me,
"The vow you made that you will be going to church, are you sure you will fulfill it?"
I said, "Yes, I will be going to church every Sunday, no matter what."
Immediately I finished saying that I saw myself on the floor and found myself at the altar.
Ngozi Christiana Njoku & Family
Deliverance Testimony
Tell us what happened afterwards.
I am very happy and I am proud to be here.
Hallelujah!
The evidence of Christ Jesus is lives changed.
You are going to tell us the differences you have seen in your life, since you received your deliverance.
Can you now tell us once again, what was the life you were living in the past and what God has done for you?
Since I was delivered, when I see a woman, I see her as a woman and when I see a man, I see him as a man.
Before, I had relationships with women and I didn't see men as men - I saw women like men.
But now, when I see women, I see them as women and men as men.
I thank God for that.
Yesterday, my brother called me and asked how much I owed for store rent since I travelled to Niegeria
and how much I owed for my house rent - I was surprised.
This has never happened to me before!
No one had called to ask of my debts to pay, I was happy!
He promised that he would pay the rent.
Hallelujah! Shall we put our hands together for Jesus!
You have just listened to this life changing testimony from our sister,
who has been separated from the kingdom of darkness.
She said that in the past she had been living a very rough life and she was bisexual.
She was attracted to women like herself.
Her life, in a nutshell, was not in accordance with God's Word.
But that is her past.
As you know, Jesus Christ enters our lives to put an end to our past and give birth to our future.
That is exactly what God has done in the life of our sister.
Today, she is testifying that her past is indeed over.
Once again, let us rejoice with our sister by putting our hands together beautifully for our Lord and Saviour -
Jesus Christ.
Before we go on, we want to listen to your advice, concerning what God has done in your life.
You mentioned your daughter, who is standing beside you.
We know she is going to be in the best position to share with us her testimony.
Before listening to her, we are going to watch TV once again, and see how she had received her deliverance.
Let us stay tuned.
DELIVERANCE TIME
The power of God flows through the faculties of Prophet T.B. Joshua,
bringing healing, deliverance and all of God's blessings into the lives of the people,
who have come to The SCOAN.
As Prophet T.B. Joshua continues to pray for them, he encounters this lady,
who immediately begins to manifest.
Let's see what happens.
Who are you that destroyed the family?!
I am a queen!
How many of you are in this body
We are four!
Fire!
I will destroy her family!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
My names are Anastasia Chinoso.
I am from Imo State, Nigeria.
I'm 18 years old.
At the age of 13 I was raped.
Since then my eyes were opened.
If I were sent to buy an egg, I would run away and never come back.
I would not come back home for one year and a month.
My mum sent some people to hold me but they would not see me.
When she sent me to school, I wouldn't go there directly.
I would just hang around with boys, smoke and drink, I would not concentrate on my education.
I was raped at the age of 13 years.
I was living a bad life, sleeping with men...
I got pregnant two times - these children were aborted.
Then my mum changed my school.
I was still living the same life, going around, smoking, going to clubs.
I would not concentrate.
When my mum was sending me anywhere, I would not come back, I would run away.
Even when I was at home with my mum, I wouldn't hear or obey her when she talked to me.
My grandmother and sisters - everybody in the family hated me because of my attitude and bad life.
They have changed my school seven times.
Seven times your mum changed your school, hoping that you would meet good friends.
Are you saying that all this did not bring any results?
Yes, she changed my school thinking that all this was because of my bad friends, but nothing changed.
That is how it was.
Friday, last week my mum told me that we would be going to T.B. Joshua.
I said OK.
In the afternoon, at around 3 o'clock she went out.
Then I decided not to go to T.B. Joshua.
My friend took me out of the house.
Since then my mum has been calling, to ask where I was.
I did not answer her calls.
She called one of my friends, asking her to bring me because we were expected to go to T.B. Joshua.
My friend said OK.
My friend called me and told me that my mum was looking for me and to go back home.
I said that I heard the message.
My mum called me again but I didn't pick up the phone.
Five minutes later my mum called me again.
I didn't want to pick up the phone because I didn't want to go anywhere.
So, what finally happened?
Five minutes later I was going home.
I called my mum before reaching home.
I told her that I was very sorry and I didn't want go back home because I was afraid that she would beat me.
She said, that I should come back home and that she would not beat me.
She said that we were going somewhere - I said "OK".
I came back home and then we entered the night bus and came here.
While entering the church, T.B. Joshua was coming near me.
I was so afraid.
I felt fire - it was burning my legs and my body.
That is when T.B. Joshua prayed for me and delivered me.
Now, I'm free.
Before I had dreams of snakes and other bad things.
But now, since T.B. Joshua delivered me...
I really thank God for what He did to me.
I do not have any bad dreams anymore.
Thank You, Jesus, I'm free.
When I went out, men would sleep with me.
They would only make promises and do nothing, they would only sleep with me.
So did big men, so did little boys...
How would you describe this type of life you were living then, in one word?
I was living a bad life, I didn't attend school regularly, I didn't concentrate on my education.
You have heard from our sister that in the past she was going out with different type of men, to the extent that
she had abandoned her school, and had no focus on her education.
Her life was focused mainly on men.
That was a kind of life she was living.
We can conclude what this kind of life is all about.
After your deliverance, can you tell us the changes you have seen in yourself?
The changes I have seen in myself: I don't have bad dreams anymore, I don't go out, I don't smoke or drink.
I really thank God for what T.B. Joshua did for me.
I really appreciate what he did for me.
Parents; I really want you to always take care of your children and focus on God.
Since your deliverance - you testify that that urge you used to have,
that pushed you to go out with different kind of men,
and made you to lose focus on your education is no more?
Yes.
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus for this wonderful thing He has done in the life of this sister,
rescuing her out of the captivity of satan, and bringing her back to light.
We give glory to God what He has done in your life.
I also thank you for that wonderful advice.
This woman here is my grandmother, and this one is my lovely mother.
Let us here from the grandmum.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
I am Elizabeth Njoku.
What I learnt last week about my daughter and granddaughter was terrible.
T.B. Joshua, may God bless you, in Jesus’ name.
(Amen.)
This is my first daughter and at times, she would be angry towards me.
When I talked to her, she would get annoyed and talk back to me rudely.
Since she has been delivered, there is nothing wrong with her anymore.
What about your gran daughter?
My granddaughter always disturbed me; I even wanted to die because of her.
I prayed to God Almighty to bless this girl for me, in Jesus’ name.
Tell us more about the lifestyle she lived then.
At times, when I would take her to the farm, she would run away from the farm.
If I sent her to buy me eggs, she would buy three, so it wouldn’t be enough;
so I would send her to buy three to five more eggs then, I wouldn’t see her again.
She would go out for two weeks, before coming here.
We heard from the grandmum; to the glory of God - she told us about the kind of life
the daughter and granddaughter lived in the past, before their deliverance.
Firstly, she talked about her daughter - she said that she was possessed
and that evil spirit made her to be very angry.
This anger created a lot of problems between the daughter and herself.
Whatever she told her, she would not listen.
But since her daughter's deliverance, she has seen a big difference in her - now she is a calm person.
She was telling us also about her granddaughter, the lifestyle she lived in the past -
she would leave the house and not return in days.
Tell us more about the kind of lifestyle your granddaughter was living then.
She was smoking, drinking alcohol and going to clubs.
When I looked for her but didn’t see her, I would ask God to bring her back safely.
The woman said that when she would take her granddaughter to the farm,
she would just disappear and wouldn't be seen for days.
She then engaged in a vigorous prayer to get her granddaughter back home.
Tell us how the lifestyle of your daughter affected you.
What kind of men did you see going out and spending time with her?
How did this affect her education in her childhood?
The men were many, I cannot count them; there were a lot.
I saw a few of them and when I saw them, I drove them away from my compound.
She would get angry and ask why I drove them away and I would tell her,
"This is my house, it does not belong to you".
The grandmother is explaining that the granddaughter was living a very bad life,
she was going out with a lot of men - she cannot even give account of the number of men
she used to go out with.
A lot of men would throng in her compound to see her granddaughter.
She would have to spend time driving these men away from her compound, making it known to them clearly
that this house belonged to her and not them, so they should not come to her compound again.
Tell us more, madam.
At my age, I was born in 1960, it was not easy to look after her.
God used T.B. Joshua to settle everything that has to do with her.
So, I too am free, in Jesus' name!
Madam, can you now tell us once again, since your daughter's deliverance, tell us exactly
what are the changes, big differences, you have noticed in the life of your granddaughter?
She had anger before but now, she is at peace with her mother.
She has really changed now, in Jesus' name.
Sister, can you tell us your own advice to people listening to you all over the world?
My advice to the world is, I will use what Prophet T.B. Joshua said last Sunday,
for gold to be gold, it must face challenges and to face challenges you need faith.
People all around the world, have faith – distance is not a barrier.
Leave your beauty, leave your pride and everything behind – just come to God;
confess your sins and be free just as I did, in Jesus' name.
Ngozi Christiana Njoku & Family
Deliverance Testimony
We heard from our sister; no matter the problem or situation you face in life - you should run to God,
and He is able to see you through.
Yes, we give glory to God for what He has done in your life and we thank you for a wonderful advice.
We want to advise you - that God Almighty has taken you out of the kingdom of darkness and brought you
into the Kingdom of Light - the primary reason for this is the salvation of your soul.
Make sure you stand firm in the Word of God, make His Word a foundation of your life and your home
and that Word will continue to set you on the good road to the good life.
Once again, let us put our hands together beautifully for our Lord and Saviour, Jesus Christ,
for what He has done in the life of this family.
RV: Mel Flowers 16/03/2019